What the hell?
What are you doing, Varun?
Instead of treating him first,
you've been treating a terrorist?!
I was just trying to treat him.
He has got JVP laceration
and a flail chest.
He can't be saved.
But in his case, only the hand is injured.
A simple amputation
can save his life.
Do you know who is he?
Retd. Col. Sandeep Gowda's son!
So what? Why are you
getting emotional about it?
Let's be practical.
Despite making an effort, he will die.
Instead, we can save him and
gather information in the future.
Just think practically.
Proceed!
I've reached a decision
after thinking this through.
We're not a good match.
Let's call off this wedding. Bye.
The number you have dialed is currently
busy. Please try again later.
SIX MONTHS AGO
Her beautiful face caught my attention
I was enchanted when her shadow grazed me
Do you always fasten
the top button of your shirt?
Isn't that the purpose of it?
Sure.
I've sent a gift for you.
I know it's a gift.
But what is it?
It's a book called
How To Be Perfect In Life.
You look extremely disciplined.
What time do you usually
wake up in the morning?
At 4:30 a.m.
Is it because you deliver
milk in the morning?
No, I wake up to study.
Study!
-You look beautiful.
-Thank you.
No girl I have ever met
Has killed me with her beauty
And then resurrected me
No girl I have ever met
Has killed me with her beauty
And then resurrected me
The time spent walking with you
Is a blessing to me
I relentlessly look for you all night
I have lost myself
After having found you
-Can I take a picture?
-Sure, go ahead.
But please delete it right after.
PRESENT DAY
Hey, don't forget to
take your lunch box.
Please don't run your mouth
out there. We'll do the talking.
I'll try my best not to.
-But I can't help it if they go overboard.
-Bye, Mom!
She's definitely going to
reject you. Stay strong!
Keep moving.
I don't know how to put it across.
It's kind of hard for us to say this.
Calling off the wedding…
is not an easy task, but…
it is good that they understood
they're not compatible with each other.
Had this been the case post marriage…
it would have been tough.
Don't generalize it.
Can you please specify
why they are not compatible?
-Well, I can't go into detail--
-Sister-in-law, let me explain it clearly.
Let them get some clarity.
Auntie, I have a few expectations
from my husband-to-be.
Would you care to elaborate?
I mean I want him to be
positive, emotional and caring.
I expected someone who
gives importance to emotions.
But, Auntie, your son
is emotionally detached.
You're too young to be
contemplating one's character.
It's based on the little things I noticed.
The other day, I sent him a text saying,
"I'm very tired and my legs are
hurting from shopping since morning."
Do you know what
his reply to that text was?
What was your reply?
Omega 350. One tablet in
the morning and one at night.
Did you hear that?
I expected a different reply from him.
"Oh, no! Your legs are hurting?!
If I were there, I would have
made you a hot cup of tea
and massaged your legs."
Auntie, I want a husband who cares,
and not just some doctor who…
prescribes medicine.
Having a doctor in the family
is a good thing, dear.
I can get a doctor's appointment
if I need to see one, Uncle.
I don't really have to get married to one.
If I face a problem with
the water supply at home,
I wouldn't just marry a plumber, right?
-Correct.
-Uncle, you can be quiet as usual.
I'll talk to Auntie about it.
Mini…
I think you're mistaken about him.
Don't you say a word!
Dad doesn't like sister-in-law at all.
He didn't want you to marry her.
Because he thought if you did,
you'd become her slave.
I'm not trying to
drive a wedge between you two.
Just saying!
You still got married to her, right?
You went your own way.
Similarly, calling off
this wedding is my wish.
Sister-in-law, I like you very much.
I liked you the very first time I met you.
When your father was hospitalized,
I sent his reports to him
and asked for his opinion.
Do you know what he replied?
Ask him yourself.
What did you tell her?
I told her that he'd die
within the next 12 hours.
And just as he predicted,
he died within the next 12 hours.
Well, he was right, dear.
He did die as per the prediction.
Him passing was not an issue at all.
It's just not right to say
something so negative.
"There's nothing to worry about.
Everything will be fine."
He should say such positive things!
How can you state
a negative report as positive?
You must. You have to
be positive about it.
Positivity is everything.
If you go to a dead person
and whisper, "You're fine.
There's nothing to worry about",
they might even come back to life.
I've told you a million times
that pretty girls are stupid.
See for yourself.
Two doctors getting married
will make a perfect match.
Listen, I don't like to
beat around the bush.
Let me be honest with you.
I don't like you.
Same to you.
I'm happy that you called off the wedding.
Come on, let's go.
Let him come when he wants to.
We should leave.
My son…
They have left.
Are we done?
I'm running late.
My dad…
Son…
would you like some tea?
Do you believe in God?
I do, sir.
God has saved you
from this disastrous wedding.
If you let her into your life,
she will certainly ruin it.
You saw how she tried to turn
my daughter-in-law against me.
We will eventually be in trouble.
For our daughter's well-being, we chose
a humble prospective groom like you.
But she insulted and humiliated
you in front of everyone.
Your parents are bound to be furious.
There's nothing wrong with you.
You're well-educated, good
looking and well-behaved.
You'll find yourself a perfect match.
But she deserves to be taught a lesson.
She needs someone who can keep her
under control and break her arrogance.
Uncle, I'm an arrogant man.
-Yes, Preethi?
-Did Chinnu come home?
What are you saying?
Didn't you go to pick up her?
They said that school
was over in the afternoon.
-But I can't find Chinnu.
-What?
-I'm really scared!
-I don't get it! Are you kidding me?
-Did you ask the security guard?
-Ma'am, I checked with everyone.
-What happened?
-You stay right there. I'm coming.
-I'm coming to the school.
-What happened?
-Chinnu had a half-day school today.
And now, Preethi can't find her.
Get me my purse!
-Get over here!
-She must be at her friend's place.
-You get over here!
-Call Priya's mother.
-Please book a cab.
-I'll get my phone.
-Check if she booked a cab.
-She's on it.
I'm calling Priya.
Hello, Priya?
This is Priyanka's mother speaking.
-Did she come to your house?
-The cab will be here in three minutes.
-Okay. Can you share Samyuktha's number?
-Did you check with the driver?
Thank you, dear.
-Dad, you stay at home.
-Okay, I'll stay back.
-This way?
-Yes, it will come this way.
-What happened?
-Chinnu had a half-day at school.
She's neither at school nor did
she come home. I'm worried.
-Did you inquire at the school?
-That's where we're going.
We've booked a cab.
Cab?
Can I drop you guys in my car?
-You call your uncle. I'll call Sukanya.
-Mom, what did Preethi say?
-Is she at the school--
-Please wear your seat belt.
Is this Sukanya's mother?
This is Priyanka's mother speaking.
Is she at your place?
-Please wear your seat belt.
-Oh, is it?
-Please put Sukanya on the phone.
-Uncle, this is Navneet speaking.
-Hello? Sukanya, when did Priyanka leave?
-Chinnu had a half-day at school today.
I wanted to check if she came over.
Oh, I see.
-Ask her to call me if she comes over.
-Okay, Uncle.
Thank you, dear.
-She's not at Uncle's house.
-She didn't go to Sukanya's house.
Making a scene about the situation
or yelling at people and accusing them
of negligence is not going to help.
We have a half-day off because
the school correspondent passed away.
Please file a complaint at the police
station and start looking for your child.
We'll support you and
do everything in our power.
Let's hope for the best.
Sir, I've filed an FIR.
We've already started
to look for your daughter.
Please don't worry.
If you go into depression, it will
be difficult to find your daughter.
You have to be strong
and face the situation.
Yes?
Okay.
Muthu, remember to pick up
my daughter from the coaching class
at 5:00 p.m. tomorrow.
In case someone has kidnapped her,
they will call you either
to threaten you or demand ransom.
And if they call by any chance,
we need to track and monitor the call.
So, we'll have one of our men
stationed at your house. Okay?
-Where is Bhagat?
-He's on his way, sir.
They summon me as they please,
and they expect me to appear at once.
-Sir…
-As if I'm a sitting duck!
-What is it?
-Do you remember me, sir?
Your name is Daniel D'Souza.
You are an engine driver
at Metro Railways.
Your daughter's name
is Angelina D'Souza.
Last month on the 8th around 8:00 p.m.
your daughter went missing
on her way to school.
Age, 12. Height, 5'2". Weight, 41 kg.
She has brown eyes.
Is that enough or should I mention
the names of your ancestors as well?
-What, are you testing my memory?
-No, sir.
-I didn't mean to--
-I know where you're getting at.
You want to ask if we will
find your daughter or not.
-Yes, sir.
-Shall I lie or tell you the truth?
Please tell me the truth, sir.
If I tell you the truth,
you'll get emotional.
So, I'll lie to you.
We'll definitely find your daughter.
You should be careful
with your belongings.
I was very careful, sir.
Sir…
what is the matter?
It's been a month and half
since my daughter went missing.
We have no idea where she is
and what happened to her.
What are they saying?
They said they will let me
know if they find her.
When will they find her?
I've been asking them
the same question every day.
But they don't seem to have an answer.
Please ask them to say something!
At least ask them to tell me
if daughter has died!
Did any unknown person
visit your house recently?
Good morning, sir!
Why are you shouting?
Did you eat?
You do one thing.
Their daughter has gone missing.
Sir.
You go to their house and tap their
phone if they receive a threatening call.
Monitor it closely.
Oh, no! This has become a routine now.
You promised to recommend me
to the department.
But you've been
assigning me the same job.
How long do you expect
me to record phone calls?
When will I get to join
the department and break the record?
You're talking too much.
You don't have to do it.
-I'll send someone else.
-Oh, no!
I'll go.
Come on!
There's nothing more important
than finding your daughter.
That's enough. Go.
Hey, stay put inside the house.
Don't step out.
Shall I stay put even if
I have to use the restroom?
Everything's perfect. Final checking.
I'm hungry. I'll be back
once I'm done with my meal.
Sir, you're being irresponsible.
What if we get a call
while you're away?
Well, I'm hungry!
You just had your coffee.
Oh! So, you're keeping an account?!
This might be your first case,
but it's my 17th case.
If an eight-year-old goes missing,
she will never come back.
It's probably a case
of human trafficking.
Sir, what is human trafficking?
It means trading of human beings.
Don't tell me that someone
might call demanding a ransom!
You have three bedrooms. Each one
of you can pick one and cry in there!
No one seems to have
understood a thing I said.
Only he seems to have understood it.
He has accepted the truth and
is planning to have another child.
But… why is he locking
himself in the room?
Oh, my! You instigated
him to commit suicide!
Hey, shut up! Damn it!
Oh, God! Someone, please save him!
What happened?
Please hear me out!
Hey, go and break down the door!
I can't break down the door!
I'll end up getting hurt!
Step aside!
You better save him before I get back.
I hope everything's fine.
If you're gutsy enough
to commit suicide…
why don't you pluck up the courage
to find your daughter?
Let the police do their job.
We should also look for her.
Listen, the police
will never look for her.
They will never help
ordinary people like us.
If the child of a politician or
a commissioner had gone missing,
they would have brought down
the military to look for them.
Your second option
is the right thing to do.
Only you have to
look for your daughter.
Listen to him and look
for her as long as you can.
If you can't, then please die.
Let me see who comes to save you.
Until then, do not
take that saree off the fan.
What are you looking at?
Your niece is missing
and you're glaring at me!
Would you like it
if I do the same to you?
Irresponsible lady!
As far as I know, you think
from others' perspective.
But in this case, you're not thinking
from your daughter's perspective.
What would she think?
She has a father.
I'm sure she's hoping that you
will manage to save her somehow.
If you kill yourself, you will also be
shattering your daughter's hopes.
Oh, heart! Oh, my dear heart!
It's bound to thaw and shatter
Come closer, my dear heart!
It's bound to thaw
Oh, heart! Oh, my dear heart!
It's bound to thaw and shatter
Come closer, my dear heart!
It's bound to thaw
MISSING
Nightmares have been keeping me up
I can't stop thinking about you
This pain has shattered me into pieces
I have only suffered since you went away
The separation has left me distraught
Oh, my dear!
This pain is unbearable
I have only suffered since you went away
The separation has left me distraught
Oh, my dear!
This pain is unbearable
In the last four years,
400 girls have went missing.
It'd be a very big deal even if
ten of them had been found.
I'm being honest
because you're my friend.
You won't find your daughter.
I've asked my men
to look for your daughter.
I'm not able to do it.
It's not in my power to find her.
You keep looking for her.
That's the right thing to do.
Don't leave me and go far away
My eyes can't bear the burden of tears
I will stay by your side forever
Like a shadow
A shadow doesn't have a voice
I'm going to live a life in solitude
The pain is gut-wrenching
The memories haunt me
I'm breaking down
Nightmares have been keeping me up
I can't stop thinking about you
This pain has shattered me into pieces
I have only suffered since you went away
The separation has left me distraught
Oh, my dear!
This pain is unbearable
I have only suffered since you went away
The separation has left me distraught
Oh, my dear! This pain…
Navneet, I feel your pain, brother.
I've informed all the officials about it.
They'll find your daughter for sure.
But the MLA is expecting some money.
So, pay him six lakh rupees
as compensation.
Subramani, he's my friend.
Make sure everything goes well.
Oh, heart! Oh, my dear heart!
It's bound to thaw and shatter
Come closer, my dear heart!
It's bound to thaw
Oh, heart! Oh, my dear heart!
That was not Chinnu.
Come closer, my dear heart!
It's bound to thaw
Colonel, I had mentioned
about a missing girl, right?
This is her father and this is--
This is my medical check-up
report from last week.
Give me your opinion.
Your creatinine and
uric acid levels are high.
You ought to reduce your alcohol intake.
What if I don't?
You'll die soon.
Okay.
Now, tell me.
A girl has gone missing.
That's her father, that's her
mother and that's Padmini.
Hello, sir.
-Fiancée?
-Ex-fiancée, Colonel.
Alright, I'll speak to the commissioner
and ask him to pressurize the team.
They will just add two more
police officers in the search.
That's it.
There's no guarantee
that we'll find the girl.
It seems you already
have a plan in place.
What are you going to do?
Kidnapping.
He wants to kidnap
the commissioner's daughter!
Instead of finding a way to find Chinnu,
he's planning to get all of us in trouble.
He wants to abduct the commissioner's
daughter because our child is missing!
Damn that guy!
He pegs himself as a genius.
You know how bizarre this sounds?
It's like being advised to change
undies to get rid of knee pain!
Absolutely ridiculous!
I wonder how someone can
come up with such an idea!
He has no sense whatsoever…
We have no sense.
That's why God has
sent you here as a blessing.
I'm getting late for the meeting.
See you around.
If we happen to find Chinnu
during the process…
I'll have you know that I don't intend
to use it to my advantage to marry you.
I thought of letting you know.
So, I did.
Okay.
We all are aware
what we are about to do.
We may think about a million things
before performing a surgery.
But once the blade touches the body…
without having second thoughts or
wondering whether we'll succeed or fail,
we should keep doing our job like a robot.
In a situation like this,
emotion is your worst enemy.
We ought to detach
ourselves from emotions.
Okay?
How can we do something
without having emotions?
Feelings, love, care…
all of this matters, you know?
In our mission to find Chinnu,
I'm the commander and
you people are the soldiers.
So, you will only listen
to me and follow my orders.
Discipline in military
is of the utmost importance.
And I don't like you
talking to me like that.
Get up and get out.
What?
Are you going or shall I leave?
Dear!
I hope you people are okay with it.
Now that we've decided to risk our lives,
it doesn't matter if we get hanged
to death or die in an accident.
It's all the same.
He threw me out too.
If you do as I say,
I'll pay you 1000 rupees.
If you come and beg along
with me, I'll pay you 3000 rupees.
Oh, God!
Fine, I'll pay you 5000 rupees.
Do you really think
I'll toil to make 5000 rupees?
How much do you want?
Can you pay me 10,000 rupees?
You didn't tell me who you are.
If I tell you who I am,
I'll give you 10,000 rupees.
If I don't, then I'll
give you 20,000 rupees.
I don't care about your identity.
Do you know to play cricket?
Do you know to bowl?
Hey, little boy! How are you?
If I strike, I'll score a boundary!
-Kid, please move aside.
-Did you watch the CSK match?
-It was super!
-Camera 1. The view is clear.
-Camera 2 and 3, be ready.
-Dhoni, rocked the match!
Dhoni is in position.
But no one has recognized him yet.
Be alert.
Dhoni?
Don't mention it to anyone.
Okay!
Let's go.
Hey, Dhoni is here!
That's great, kids! Okay!
One by one!
Okay, good!
Navneet, don't panic.
Keep calm and do it casually.
Take out the handkerchief from your pocket
and hold it against the girl's
nose and mouth for ten seconds.
Be cool. Don't be scared.
Kids, one by one!
-Dhoni! One autograph, please!
-Dhoni!
Dhoni, please give me an autograph!
Dhoni, I want your autograph!
Oh, my God!
Hey! Uncle, please return my bat!
Uncle, please give it back to me!
Please stop!
Uncle, give it back to me!
-Uncle!
-Hey!
Stop running!
Come on, start the car!
We didn't come here to filch this bat!
-Put on the mask!
-Sorry. Yeah, give me that.
Uncle, please return my bat!
Uncle, my bat!
Where's my bat?
Where have you people
been all this while?
-We went to the movies.
-To the movies?!
You were about to hang yourself yesterday.
And today, you went to the movies!
Are you planning to have
a family picnic tomorrow?
Idiot!
What's in that sack?
We bought popcorn.
Popcorn? It looks like a bag full of crap!
Why would you need
such a big sack for popcorn?
Untie the sack.
Will you open it or
should I call the police?
Damn it! How did he find out?
-Hey, stop gawking at me!
-Who tied the sack?
-I did.
-Just do as I say!
Don't you dare try to scare a policeman,
or you'll be done for!
You bring the sack inside
the house. I'll talk to him.
What will you say to me?
Why the hell are you pushing me?
Will you hit me? How dare
you lay a hand on a cop!
Get inside. Come on, hurry.
We kidnapped the AC's daughter.
Why the hell did you
kidnap the AC's daughter?
Didn't you say that the police won't
bother looking for ordinary people,
but they'll hunt down the kidnapper
if it's one of their own?
Correct.
If the AC's daughter is missing,
they will only look for her.
How would that help
in finding Chinnu?
We can find out the process
of hunting down a kidnapper.
How?
You have a police walkie-talkie.
Oh!
So, that's your plan!
What if the police hunt you down first?
You people will get caught.
What will you do then?
Don't worry.
I swear I won't rat you out.
Well, you should tell about me!
Everyone should know that I was
the mastermind behind this kidnapping.
Only then will they
be careful with Bhagat.
By the time the case comes to an end,
I should either chase the criminal as a
police, or chase the police as a criminal!
Hey, I'm talking to you!
Why won't you pay heed to me?
We'll make them run, sir.
Sir, we caught them.
-We're checking the vehicles now.
-We've arrested everyone in this area.
-Right here, at J7 police station.
-Name of the accused is Ramanujam.
-That's right, sir.
-Okay, sir.
We're on the lookout, sir.
Hey, check that vehicle!
Sir, we have nabbed
four people until now.
You're Dhoni, right?
So, you won't answer me!
How dare you engage in kidnapping?
I'll skin you alive!
You had been decently
begging all this while.
You should have continued it.
Why did you engage in kidnapping?
-Hey, get him something to eat.
-Okay, sir.
Would you like to eat something, Dhoni?
What are you saying?
Hey, hit it right!
I bet 500 rupees on you.
Don't you worry, I'm right here.
Come on, man! Do it!
You managed to strike again.
Now it's my turn.
Come on.
Philip, don't be scared.
Don't lose this game,
or I'll lose 500 rupees.
Come on, strike it hard!
Don't spare him.
He's totally hopeless!
You, moron! Don't you
understand what I am saying?
You look like an owl
hanging on a noose.
Hey, don't you think twice
before placing a bet?
Didn't you think twice
before kidnapping a girl?
Do you have a warrant?
Start the jeep.
Come on! Step out of the van.
Get out of here!
-Buddy!
-Yes, brother?
Business is dull these days.
-Karma is a boomerang.
-Karunas?
I said karma, not karunas.
Earlier, someone else would take the heat
for the kidnapping done by us.
Now someone else has done the kidnapping
and we're bearing the brunt of it!
The police have kidnapped me
more than I've kidnapped people.
-What is this case about?
-The AC's daughter has been kidnapped.
Someone kidnapped the AC's daughter?!
As if there's a scarcity of girls in town!
Who has the audacity
to kidnap the AC's daughter?
Oh, no!
That moron stepped
on my foot. Damn it!
Sir, we have arrested all
the kidnappers in the city.
I'm sure one among
them is the kidnapper.
One of you has messed
with a police officer's family.
The culprit's hands will be severed!
Eat it.
Please eat it, dear.
That girl has been crying unceasingly.
I feel sorry for her.
You feel sorry for her?
Well then, drop her home.
I'll get going.
No. That's not what I meant.
I just said that I feel pity for her.
I've been working day in, day out
since your niece went missing.
Don't you feel sorry for me?
-She hasn't eaten anything since morning--
-She'll eat when she is hungry.
-Do you feel sorry for her too?
-No.
I'm having fun.
We're not on a vacation to have fun.
Go!
You yell at me all the time.
I'm leaving.
-Go.
-Stop smiling!
Wear your damn masks!
Sir, you're beating up the wrong guy!
Sir, we're not the kidnappers!
Oh, God! Sir, it hurts!
One minute! They have found the girl.
You don't say!
I've been telling you since the beginning.
A professional kidnapper
would never do such a thing.
But you didn't listen to me.
Stop right there!
Preethi, pretend to be unconscious.
Hey, step out of the van!
Do not step out of the van
until I ask you to.
Stop staring at me. Get out!
Sir, Preethi is unconscious.
We have to take her to the hospital.
Didn't you hear me?
Enough with the nonsense!
-Please, sir.
-Step outside, I said!
Come on, let's get down.
I think they have an emergency.
We'll find another vehicle.
Please get down.
-Sir, please believe me…
-Hey, spectacles! Get down, man!
-You too, woman!
-I'm not lying, sir.
Hey, I'm going to kill you.
Hey, Killi! Come on, hurry up!
Why are you pleading with them?
She has fainted. We have
to take her to the hospital.
Oh, really?
Hey, drag her out of the van!
Hey, why you don't get it?
Hey, stop touching her!
Just pick her up.
-Hold her properly.
-Sir, she has fainted.
Enough with your drama!
Pull her out of the van.
It's like a truck inside
this shared transport!
-Hey, get her out.
-Sir, I don't want any trouble.
How dare you lay a hand on me!
-Come on.
-Hey, that's enough. Put him in the van!
You guys are pissing me off!
I asked you to gag him, and
you let him bite your finger!
You're being rather unprofessional.
If you continue to be like this,
you'll be a worthless rogue.
Hey, Killi! What the hell is this?
-Idiot!
-Damn it!
You didn't notice the gun
and pulled a knife at him!
What if he had shot you?
Sir…
I think you're in a hurry.
You may leave.
Hey, put the lady back in the van.
Brother, there's no need.
I can get in there by myself.
It was all a part of the plan, right?
You're up to something.
He has been screaming a lot.
We'll take the corner seat.
Could you please drop us on the way?
-You don't want him to scream, right?
-Yes.
Die! Die, idiot!
You're doomed!
Step aside.
Hey, you knocked him out with such ease.
I have to present him in an hour.
One hour is difficult. He'll regain
consciousness in two hours.
And if he doesn't, then
call me at 9445471051.
I'll tell you what to do.
-Hey, Killi, did you note it down?
-You didn't?
Note it down, you dimwit!
Hey!
What?
-Do you know to read?
-I do.
Do you have some
medicine for hair loss?
Just say yes or no.
Why are you glaring at me?
Am I?
-They beat us to a pulp!
-Are you alright?
Shall I show you my rear?
Kamalakannan! Kamesh! Pratap!
The three of you,
get over here and wait!
Oh, God!
-Why did you call us?
-What's it, brother?
The AC wants to apologize to you guys.
He doesn't have to apologize.
Tell him that I've forgiven him.
Hey! If AC is making an
apology, you gotta take it!
If you don't, they'll take you
back in there and thrash you!
Do you wanna risk it?
Get inside!
Do you have a license for that gun?
License?
Isn't it illegal to have
a gun without a license?
Do you think it's legal to kidnap
the commissioner's daughter?
Until we find Chinnu,
everything we do is illegal.
How much did you score in the 10th grade?
I get it.
I shouldn't ask any questions, right?
How long do we have to wait?
Why are they still here?
Sir, we'll leave from here
once you apologize.
Sir, look at their arrogance!
Their demand is that you and your
family have to apologize to them!
They won't leave the station
until you do so!
This guy is especially stubborn!
He has been asking about you.
You want me to apologize?
Did you see how he pushed
that cupboard on to me?
Sir, please get in.
I'll take you to the hospital.
Hey, we didn't ask for your help.
-You three look wiped-out.
-Pratap! Kamalakannan! Kamesh!
Why is he calling out our names again?
Get over here! The IG
wants to apologize to you guys.
Hey, get in the van!
Brother, please scoot over.
Sir, please have some coconut water.
Who are you?
I'm Navneet.
Navneet?
Are you the Prime Minister?
I'm the girl's father.
Please drink this.
This girl's name is Priyanka.
Last Wednesday at 12:00 p.m.
she was kidnapped when she was
leaving from St. Francis Xavier School.
Oh, no! Who the hell was it?
We tracked down cell phones
of all the kidnappers in the city…
and your cell phone signals were
close to the tower near the school.
So, one among the three of you
has kidnapped this girl.
If you confess to the crime…
I'll put back the kidneys that
I removed from your bodies.
I don't get it.
I'll return your kidneys, and
stitch it back into your bodies.
Did you just say that
you took our kidneys?
What did he remove?
He removed our kidneys.
That's it, right?
He didn't take our phones
or wallets, right?
You buffoon! Don't you
know what a kidney is?
We have two kidneys.
He has taken just one.
We can live with the one we still have.
Listen, man. We are drunkards.
Even four kidneys
won't be enough for us.
How will you live with just one kidney?
Hey, stop joking now.
You bloody…
Please don't panic.
Your stitches will
slowly start to come off.
I think one has already snapped.
Two more snaps and you're dead!
I don't understand anything.
For the last three days, I've been getting
flogged for the things I didn't do.
Now you've removed our kidneys
and you're blackmailing us.
Don't be scared.
It's very simple.
Which one of you has kidnapped the girl?
If you confess to the abduction,
I'll plant the kidneys
back into your bodies.
You'll plant them back?!
Sir…
I kidnap children from poor families…
and sell them to rich couples
who can't have children.
Sir, a lot of kids have become
millionaires because of me.
Sir, I'm only doing social service.
Do you think you're God?
Nincompoop!
Don't think that they'll
commemorate you with a statue.
Listen, I have no idea about these two.
But I didn't kidnap her.
Well, then, prove that you didn't.
How?
What were you doing
on that day at that time?
I was going home to meet my wife.
Give me your wife's phone number.
This is your husband, Pratap.
I know, you pig! What is it?
Where did I come to meet you
on Wednesday afternoon?
You came where I was waiting for you.
Yes, but mention the place.
Hey! Don't you know the place?
How did you even get there?
I would rather live with one kidney
than live with you!
Where were you?
I was drinking with a friend.
Give me that friend's phone number.
90031…
You guys still have time.
If one among you agrees to the crime…
I'll return your kidneys and let you go.
If you don't, I'll take
the other kidney as well.
Understood?
Sir!
I kidnapped her.
Please forgive me.
Sir, please give us back our daughter!
Brother, please give us back our daughter!
Sir, at least tell us where she is!
-Please, brother!
-Please, sir!
Sorry, I don't have
your daughter with me.
-I handed her over to someone else.
-Oh, my God!
-To whom?
-I have no idea.
If there's a demand, they'll call me.
They'll give me a location for the drop.
And then, they'll pay up
and take the girl from me.
Tell them that you'll return the money
and ask them to return the girl.
They won't give her back.
We can't even talk to them.
Come on! Stop pleading with him!
Just shoot him if he doesn't cooperate.
They'll immediately return the girl.
Hey!
If you threaten them, they'll ask you
to shoot me and they'll hang up on you.
Loser!
Doctor… call them and tell them
that you have another girl for sale.
Ask them to come and take her.
They won't refuse.
-Hello?
-Brother, I have a girl for sale.
She's around ten or eleven
years old. Are you interested?
Didn't you sell one girl
just the day before yesterday?
And you got another one already?
At this rate, you won't spare
even one girl in this city.
You're a great kidnapper!
From now on, you're not just Kannan.
You're Kidnapper Kannan!
Fine, I'll tell you tomorrow
where to come.
Okay.
Look, I have 15 years
of experience in this field.
Now return my kidney
and I'll be on my way.
No, brother.
You're more experienced in this matter.
So, you better stick around
until we find Chinnu.
-And your kidney will be with him.
-With him?
Hey, are you kidding me?
You promised to return my
kidney if I gave you an idea.
Will you take my idea
and keep my kidney as well?
As if you're a genius
for us to celebrate you!
Hey!
If you don't stop rambling,
I'll flush your kidney down the toilet!
Are you insane?
You're capable of doing that.
By the way, you told them
that you had another girl.
-Do you have one?
-No!
-She's right here.
-What?
What you've done to me is unfair!
You obviously can't pull
off Kamal Haasan's look.
Sir!
Please don't bother.
Have you practiced
to use the injection?
Why don't you teach me again?
Look closely, sir.
One, the needle should pierce well.
Two, the drug should enter the body.
One, two.
-One, two.
-Well, that's easy!
Give me that. It's no big deal.
What about the driver?
Driver!
Oh, God!
I'm sure this scatterbrain
won't do it right.
-I know.
-What did you say?
Well, you're wearing pigtails.
If we add flowers…
-Sit.
-You took it away.
Hey, what an awful face!
What the hell are you
spraying on my face?
You kept dodging
when I tried to jab you!
How dare you mock me!
Hey, you didn't do it right,
and you're blaming him!
Don't knock him too hard.
He might forget everything.
Hey, doctor, that girl…
Doctor, ask him where
the girl is right now.
The girl is not with me, sir.
I gave her away to someone else.
Who is that?
Hey, that's such an awful face!
We can never do
business with this face.
Is my face not worth the business?
Do you expect me to abduct
Trisha to run your business?
Bhagat!
He's pissing me off!
Call up the person
who has the girl now.
Sir, we can't reach them
over the phone.
Then?
They call us when required.
They inquire about the availability.
And if we have the girls,
they fix a place and time.
At that specified time,
we ought to take the
girls and drop them off.
What else do you know about them?
Sir, they're very dangerous.
They don't feel any remorse, sir.
-What is it?
-Brother…
Chinnu does that too.
She likes to lick
Horlicks out of her hand.
When I saw you do the same…
I remembered Chinnu.
I'm sure you won't
remove Chinnu's kidney.
Stop that drama.
Go away and do your work.
-Do you have a girl?
-Yes, I do.
Friday night, 11 o'clock.
-Koyembedu bus stand.
-Okay, sir.
Sir, what are you doing?
I'm taking my suitcase.
Dear, what are you doing
over there? Come here.
Sir, take your hands off.
Madam, please stand near your suitcase.
Sir, this is our suitcase. Let it go.
When we bumped into each other,
our suitcases got swapped.
Hey, don't piss me off, man!
Show some respect.
Don't be rude.
Dad, please open the suitcase.
We'll know whose it is.
Sir, please stop meddling.
I'm not meddling.
-Let's just call the police and settle it.
-That will be nice.
Listen, if they claim it's their suitcase…
then let them just take it.
Please go ahead, sir.
It's funny that I need your
permission to take my suitcase!
Please leave, madam.
Let's go, dear.
You may go, madam.
I have to wait for the practice.
Hello.
Varun, we'll enter
the tunnel in ten seconds.
Everyone, please be ready.
Hey!
What the hell!
That is not my problem.
Hey, be careful.
Watch and learn.
I have 15 years of training.
You can jab the needle now.
Come on, lie down here.
Who switched on the lights
before we could jab him?
Oh, God!
Varun! Varun, can you hear me?
We'll hit the next tunnel in 60 seconds.
The next tunnel is 60 seconds away.
What do we do
for the next 60 seconds?
Fight!
Do you want to find Chinnu or not?
Oh, no!
Oh, my God!
I'll save you all.
Hey!
I'm going to knock him out.
-Hit him!
-Idiot.
-Sorry, dear.
-Go!
Hey, baldie! Stand still!
Oh, my!
Sorry.
Oh, no! That was a strong punch!
Oh, God!
Hey, baldie!
-Hey, Pratap!
-What is it?
-I saved you, Pratap.
-Are you serious, Bhagat?
Oh, my! Your ear is bleeding.
Damn it! Hey, do you
see what's happening?
Why do we even have to endure this?
You could have
just had another baby.
You're killing my mother's son
to save your daughter.
Who will answer my mother?
Give me your address.
I'll go and inform her.
You won't be able to speak
if I break your jaw!
Bhagat!
-Bhagat!
-Doctor, I'm here! Who should I beat up?
Oh, no!
It's pitch-dark in here!
How did they manage to
thrash people in the dark?
Doctor!
Please return my goggles!
Doctor, please ask them
to switch on the lights.
Oh, my God!
Pratap…
Pratap!
Bhagat, keep quiet.
-Pratap…
-Keep quiet, Bhagat.
-Pratap, doctor had called me.
-Good.
I went to him
thinking it was an emergency.
He took away my night-vision goggles.
Bhagat!
You were saying something, and you
took away my night-vision goggles.
It's really dark here.
Please give it back.
Who's that?
Excuse me.
I know everyone is seated here.
I can't see at the moment,
but I'm sure you can see me.
You can hold my hand and guide me.
Instead, you guys are keeping mum
and holding your breath.
This isn't fair.
Please have some mercy on me.
Hel…
Baldie!
Sorry, sir. I have
nothing to do with that kid.
It's just a rod!
Just because I'm helpless,
you're taking advantage of me.
Vadapalani!
They switched on the lights.
Is it interval now?
You have the child. Give her
back to us and I'll let you live.
If you don't, I'll slit your throat.
Do you think we'll spill the beans
because you're threatening to kill?
Alvin, if he kills me, then
you too slit your throat and die.
Don't give up the girl at any cost.
Do you think he'll kill himself
just because you asked him to?
The two of you have a great bond.
Danny, open the doors.
-I won't let go of you.
-Let go!
Melvin!
Hey!
Why are you wailing
just for just two stitches?
He ripped my flesh, removed
my kidney and bottled it up.
But I'm keeping calm, right?
Be calm, man!
He's wailing like a buffalo.
Sister, please pass me some water.
Oh, my God!
You ave a black eye!
You refused to get
married to him, right?
Now no one will be
willing to marry you.
That includes me.
Doctor, even if we
end up finding Chinnu…
you've turned us into
people beyond recognition.
Educated people are always dangerous.
It will be fine in three to four days.
How will I present myself until then?
As if people have been noticing you.
Doctor, could you please
pass me some water?
I've been asking everyone
for the last one hour.
Get lost! Psycho… doctor.
Psycho doctor!
I thought you would remove his kidney
and extract information on Chinnu,
but you're feeding him!
His brother is more important
to him than his kidney.
He'll confess very soon.
You just go and tend to the injured.
Alvin! Alvin!
Where are you?
Please say something.
Tell me, Alvin! Where are you?
I've been feeling
really scared without you.
Let's give up that girl.
Let's give them back their child.
Alvin, please say something.
Pass me that phone.
I will give up the girl.
Tell me, which one
of these girls is your child?
-Tell me, who is it?
-Hey, there's Chinnu!
-Chinnu!
-Which one?
Hurry up! We don't have much time.
-Tell him Chinnu is right behind him.
-Chinnu…
Come on!
-Chinnu is right there.
-Hurry up. Tell me fast!
I don't have much time. Hurry up!
-Chinnu!
-Please tell him.
-I want you to give up all the girls.
-What?
All the girls?!
I got permission only to give up one girl.
I can only take one girl out of here.
Now don't waste time
and make up your mind.
-Please, sir, that's my daughter.
-Come on, don't waste my time!
-Tell me fast.
-Chinnu!
I want all the girls.
Release all of them.
What is wrong with you?
We just want Chinnu to be released.
Just ask them to release Chinnu.
Don't be crazy!
Sir, he's ready to release one girl.
Please ask him to release Chinnu.
In the next ten minutes, this
container will be dispatched to Goa.
-Hurry up!
-Sir… please!
-Please, sir…
-Come on, hurry up!
Bhagat!
Hey!
Stop it!
-Stop!
-Give up all the girls.
You can kill me if you want,
but he can't give up all the girls.
That container is not under our control!
-Sir!
-Son, don't be unreasonable.
-Sir…
-We have worked so hard to find Chinnu.
Now she's right in front of our eyes,
and we're not doing anything.
You don't consider
the other girls as human beings?
Can you give up all the seven girls…
or not?
I can't.
What should I do to
have all the girls released?
If you wish to free all of them,
you'll have to go to Goa.
-Hey!
-Sir!
Why do we have to
listen to you all the time?
Chinnu is all that matters to us!
We really don't care what
happens to the other girls!
I don't need your permission
to release that guy.
Hey!
You shouldn't be shouting unnecessarily.
I'll hack you to pieces
and put you inside a glass jar.
Mini…
tell me what we should do.
Why don't we just get Chinnu released?
Oh! So, all your love and affection
is limited to your family.
You're selfish.
You don't care what happens
to the other kids.
You're all talk and no action.
Aren't you ashamed?
I only care about two things.
We will either be happy
by saving all the seven girls.
Or we will die
in the process of saving them.
That makes you
a compassionate psycho!
Brother, you've done
a lot for this family.
Please do us one last favor.
I can't bear to see my
daughter in this state.
I'm begging you! Please help us!
Please bring our daughter back!
Please save our daughter!
Sir, that's my daughter. Please, sir.
-It's our Chinnu, sir. Please help us.
-Okay.
I'll give you another option
that might make you happy.
I won't be at peace if
I abandon the other six girls.
So, one of you can pick up
that gun and shoot me.
And then, you can take back
your daughter from them.
God bless you.
Son… what's wrong with you?
Please don't waste time.
Hurry up.
I'm sure this gun is unloaded.
That's why you're being so cool about it.
Instead of going to
prison for killing you…
I'd rather go to Goa.
This is the plan, and this
is how it's going to be done.
Your plan maybe extensive,
but we don't have enough manpower.
And this guy is a troublemaker!
What do we do about others?
Fold your legs. The doctor
might perform a surgery on you.
We'll find someone along the way.
As if people are lining up
out there to save the child.
No one will agree to it.
I agree they won't.
We should make them
an offer they can't refuse.
But we need a scapegoat.
He is not your father.
And you are not her husband.
And this woman is not her sister-in-law.
To sum up, you people
are not of the same family.
You're pretending to be a family
and you're kidnapping kids.
Why is everyone injured
in some way or the other?
We met with an accident
last week during a kidnapping.
Who was driving?
Don't you have any sense?
There were so many women in the car.
You should've been more careful.
Look over there.
A beautiful face has been scarred.
You should kick him out of the house.
We tried, but he doesn't leave.
You people are injured.
Go over there and settle down.
So, tell me.
What can I do for you?
According to the information he received,
a man has kidnapped a lot of girls
in Goa and taken them hostage.
If we plan well and rescue them…
he can't file a police complaint,
and we won't face any issues either.
The total worth
of those girls is 50 crore rupees.
According to your plan,
we'll be at greater risk.
What did I tell you?
They're small-time goons
who just play with sickles.
They're bound to get nervous if you
discuss a deal worth millions with them.
A dog can only bark.
But a lion can kill.
We can't use them to kidnap children.
We can only use their faces
to scare off children.
What a waste of time!
Hey! Don't forget that
you're in my hood!
-So?
-Sir, please.
It's okay.
I usually don't give my word to anyone.
But when I do, I would
risk my life to fulfill it.
I'll fulfill it even if I'm dead.
You can't fulfill it if you die.
-We can only light candles for you.
-Correct!
Hey, you've been giving your
word like it's a piece of cake!
It's not easy to get beaten up.
Killi…
I'll rip you apart.
How do we split the share?
33%
34%
Let's do it this way.
40%
30%
This is just like someone stealing
a story and calling it their own.
I bring the project to you guys,
and you call the shots?!
-I'm leaving. This won't work out.
-Sir, please don't get angry.
-I'll talk to him.
-Carry on.
Sir, I really don't care about the share.
This alliance matters the most to me.
I want to use that
for bigger projects in the future.
So, it will be 20% for me…
40% for you…
-and 40% for him.
-Wrong!
Listen to this.
41%
21%
38%
Hey!
That's a rather bizarre way
to split the shares!
I've never heard something like this!
Dim-witted dweeb!
-Mr. Pratap! Please, sir!
-Shut up, man!
God knows if he's splitting shares
or rambling landline numbers!
-Such bizarre numbers…
-Sir, excuse me.
Why are you overdoing it?
If you don't listen to him,
I'll take out your second kidney as well!
Listen, if I agree to all his terms,
he'll figure out the ruse.
He will cave in only if we play hardball.
-That's why I did that.
-Why are you guys arguing?
We know that there's
no actual money involved.
It doesn't matter even if we
give him 100% of the share.
-He'll get on board in no time.
-Give him 100% of the share?!
To give him 100% of the share,
why are we risking
our lives for this kidnapping?
Just for charity!
Oh, God! He's incorrigible!
I'm ready to do anything you ask me to.
Just make sure he's not a part of it.
I had a word with him.
Your deal is fine with us.
-Ask that girl to say the same.
-Why?
Mahali's rules will
keep changing with time.
Wrong!
I meant that girl.
Thought so.
He is fond of her.
You tell me, dear.
Why are you seeking his permission
as if he's your legal husband?
What's your name?
Sumathi.
For Sumathi, I'm okay with this deal.
What time are we leaving for Goa?
GOA
-Hello?
-I've emailed you a photo.
The person in that picture
will be at the resort.
Make sure he doesn't spot
you guys. Be careful.
Okay.
He has emailed a photo.
He has asked us to make sure we
don't get spotted by that person.
Excuse me.
I hope I didn't disturb you guys.
Tamil?
Are you coming to this
resort for the first time?
Thanks for choosing our resort.
Goa is a very beautiful place.
There are many places and things
to see and explore out here.
If you wish to explore something…
you can contact
the reception anytime.
And since you're at my
resort for the first time,
I would like to inform you
that your breakfast will be
complimentary for the rest of your stay.
So, please enjoy your
stay with us. Thank you.
Hi, good morning.
How are you doing?
-Hello?
-Yeah?
Actually, he spotted us.
Wonderful! Now please
hang up for God's sake.
Wait a minute!
He doesn't seem to be
a bad person like you mentioned.
He seems like a decent man.
Also, he's very sweet.
I hope we're doing the right--
You look like a genius.
But are you really a genius?
Just follow the plan.
Tonight at 10 o'clock.
Killi, imagine how it would be if
we kidnap Sumathi instead of Mini.
You'll be happy,
and I'll be pissed off.
Listen, stick to the doctor's plan.
When they look at the CCTV footage,
it should look like real kidnapping.
Wait and watch. I'm going to
grab her by the neck and kidnap her.
That girl is calling us.
Hello! It's the big car on your right.
I can see you. Keep walking.
It's the big car.
You're heading the wrong way.
Walk towards the car!
I'm almost there, and you
haven't opened the door yet.
-Hey!
-Come on, Mahali! Nab her!
Hey, Killi! My pants are stuck.
Oh, no! My daughter is missing.
Did anyone see her?
-Mr. Foreigner…
-Check at the reception.
-have you seen her?
-You people are irresponsible!
My daughter went
missing from your resort.
-Sir, please don't panic.
-I'm going to file a police complaint.
-I want to file a complaint right away!
-Please calm own. We'll take care of it.
Sir, I can understand.
Please give us some time.
How can you ask me for time?
It's my daughter who has gone missing!
It's imperative that we
file a police complaint!
Are you going to help me or not?
Sir, I'm really sorry about this.
It's not an ordinary thing
for a girl to go missing.
I can totally understand your pain.
But please try to
understand my situation.
If you file a police complaint, the name
of my resort will be out in the news.
And it will ruin my
entire reputation.
And it will ruin my entire business.
Sir, just trust me and
give me eight hours.
I have many friends in
the government and the police department.
I'll handle this unofficially
and find your daughter, sir.
Please consider me as your son
and give me some time.
Sir, it's on the CCTV.
Yeah, Terry?
Gabbar, you have six hours. Find them.
Okay!
Killi, kidnapping the girl
was not the big task.
Now they'll take us away
and beat us to a pulp.
If we bear their thrashing,
we can earn their trust.
That's what the doctor said.
Doctor said they would
be here before noon.
It's 15 minutes past noon,
and no one's here yet!
Where's the girl? Tell me!
-Shall I confess, Mahali?
-Don't confess, Killi.
I've given my word.
For Sumathi!
You're too old to be
romancing, damn it.
Terry, if we beat
them more, it'll be fatal.
They're bloody scoundrels.
Not able to break them.
Boss, they're
going to start afresh.
-Get out!
-Sir, please spare us.
-Please! Sir!
-Oh, no!
Mahali!
Oh, God!
Oh, no! Mahali!
Mahali, let's confess it.
-Don't. Please bear it all.
-Mahali, let's confess.
-I don't deserve this.
-I've given my word.
I don't deserve it.
Oh, God. That's nasty.
Word! Word! My nose!
-Oh, no!
-Boss, here use this.
Damn it, he gave
him a box to beat us.
Oh, God, no!
Bloody, scoundrel.
-Let go of me.
-Get inside, damn it.
-Oh, no!
-You wanna try this?
I appreciate that you're
not confessing it for my sake.
I love you!
Damn it, I forgot why
we're getting beaten up.
-Why don't you give me some clue?
-Hey, give me that knife.
He's getting a knife.
-He's bringing a knife, damn it.
-Knife!
I'll confess. I'll confess.
I'll confess.
Ice creams.
-Welcome, sir.
-Hello.
-Yes, sir.
-I need to talk to you.
I don't understand.
You know Tamil,
right. Shall we talk?
I can get you anything
that's on the menu.
Vanilla, strawberry,
butterscotch,
vanilla truffle, chocolate
truffle, strawberry mousse.
Tell me what you want?
Shut down the shop stating
maintenance and get rid of the customers.
Come inside.
What do you want?
Where's the girl you kidnapped
last night from my resort?
That girl has been
transferred elsewhere.
Ask me for something else.
I can't leave without the girl.
Like I mentioned, I
can't bring back the girl.
Please leave.
Hey!
Sir. Sorry, sir.
It was a mistake.
Please forgive him.
Oh, God, no!
Hey!
-Oh, God, no!
-How dare you rat me out?
I'm okay with what happened.
But one thing I don't get it.
If you were truly
a resort-owner…
you would've filed a
complaint with the police.
Instead, you seek me out and
you're here to discuss terms with me.
What I don't get is, how come
a resort-owner is go gutsy?
Either you're
police or a criminal.
If you are police…
I'm not police. That
I can promise you.
But I want to tell
you something.
It really doesn't matter if
you are a big gangster…
you can't step out of
Goa, if you shoot me dead.
All you need is just any girl.
But I want the girl
you've kidnapped.
I'll give you a girl.
You return that girl to me.
Problem solved.
How come a resort
owner is into kidnapping?
You own a ice cream parlor.
And I own a resort.
That's the only difference.
Do you still think I'm a
fool to believe your stories?
You don't have to
believe what I'm saying.
But you'll believe your eyes, right?
Keep 200 meter radius and follow them.
-How long have you been doing this?
-Twelve years!
I'm ten years senior to you.
Oh!
Keep the target in sight.
Okay, sir.
Don't get too
close to the target.
Target on sight.
Boys, you know the drill.
On my command!
Number 3!
Number 2!
The target is at 37° 06' 43'' W.
You can pick any girl you want.
They're very young girls.
Until they hit puberty,
we keep them here.
Only after that will I export them.
Virgin export.
That's the current demand.
I thought you said you're
ten years senior to me.
But your actions
state something else.
What makes you say that?
You've hardly known me for two days.
But you've already shown
me your vital hideout.
What if I turn
out be the police?
What will you do?
If you're truly police,
what would you do?
I would've come with the force.
Once I got settled inside,
I would've informed them.
They would've barged in and
took control over this place.
How long would
it take to control?
Twenty to thirty minutes.
Gabbar!
Nazeer!
In just two minutes, I would have
disposed everyone into the ocean.
Just like how they found the Titanic…
it would take years for
them to recover their bodies.
Smart.
Okay, listen all units.
DC has a fail-safe.
-What?
-Abort plan!
I feel ashamed to have
done this to one of our own.
I'll return that girl.
You don't have to
do anything in return.
After looking at your grandeur
set-up, I have an offer for you.
What is it?
In the next ten days, I have to
ship 70 girls from India to Brazil.
I have 30 girls with me.
Can you give me 40 girls?
I'm ready to pay
any price for that.
I know it's tough.
Only, if you can
pull it off, say okay.
I don't know what else is
out there. So, let's not risk it.
You guys can leave.
Thanks for coming.
We can plan and
execute it meticulously.
Hear me out!
Colonel, more than courage
we need intelligence out here.
It's fine, if you or I
die in the process.
But young lives are involved.
-So, let's not risk it.
-Talk like a military man.
Risk is a given.
I don't want a plan that saves only eight
out of ten lives.
I want a plan that
can save all 10 lives.
I'll do what suits me the best.
I don't need your advice.
You don't have the
experience that I have in this.
You will regret this.
Goodbye!
It's better think
about it ten times…
before you take a giant leap.
You've just known
him for two days.
And already he has huge demands.
What if he's a fraud?
The girls we kidnapped are
not going to go for a waste.
Only after we receive
the full settlement.
We'll deliver the girls,
If he turns out to be a fraud,
we'll burn him alive out here.
But if he's genuine, that'll
open up a new market for us.
Our business will
have a wider reach.
Okay. Let me meet him once.
An ice-cream vendor indulging
in large scale human trafficking…
I'm finding it hard to believe.
A person who is running a
huge human trafficking network…
also owns a ice cream shop.
Is this believable, uncle?
One hundred percent!
Only after you
settle the payment,
we'll board the girls
on to the containers.
If this works for you…
offer, okay!
Deal, okay!
But before we finalize the deal…
you'll have to
speak to our boss.
Okay, we'll talk to him.
But before you speak to him,
bear two things in your mind.
One. You can answer only
if you're questioned by him.
Two. You have to address
him as Don Pablo El-Fino.
Don Pablo El-Fino.
Repeat it.
-We'll repeat it to him.
-No!
He doesn't like it when people
mispronounce his name.
So, you'll have to repeat it.
Don Pablo El-Fino.
Don Pablo El-Fino, hola!
These two men have been the best
in the business for a very long time.
Don Pablo El-Fino, hola!
What happened? Why
did he shut it down?
One minute.
Dad, why didn't you
repeat what I taught you?
Son, he's a useless
supporting actor.
You chose a wrong person to act.
Hang up the phone.
Wear your lungi!
-You take your payment and leave.
-Okay.
I'm sorry. The deal is off.
Let's end it here.
Why is the deal off?
My boss is not
able to trust you.
He believes that you can't pull
off a project of this magnitude.
In how many days
did you need the girls?
In ten days.
I'll get them to you in five days.
Terry…
call all our men tomorrow.
Speak to them in Varun's presence.
Six day from today…
the girls will be been shipped.
And then, I'll speak to your boss.
You've been conning them profusely.
What if he finds out?
Definitely, he'll find out.
And when he does, he'll kill all of us.
So, why are you doing this?
But it'll take time for him to find out.
By then, we would've finished
our mission and escaped.
Plan B is now in motion.
You guys start your game!
They're going to ask me
crazy stuff like, you know…
105…
106…
107…
108…
109…
-It hurts, damn it!
-You wanted to act, right?
So, endure it.
-Enough! Take the money.
-Thank you.
Bloody, you broke my hand.
I'll practice well and return
tomorrow to defeat you.
You'll wake up in the morning.
But I doubt your hand will.
I'm going to break it.
I'll break all ten fingers.
I'm going to break his hands too.
I won't spare him.
-You can't defeat him in this life.
-Why?
You gotta be fast like a tiger!
But you're a…
tortoise.
Go and apply some
coconut oil on your hands.
Don't worry. You'll
be fine. Small bugger!
Hey, it's easy to
speak, damn it.
But in action,
you can't do squat.
-Do you know who is he?
-Who?
You don't know his
strength. Try challenging him.
-I don't have money, bro.
-I'll lend you.
There are five rules to follow.
Listen carefully.
Rule number one!
Once the game begins, the
first person to tear up will lose.
Rule number two!
Freedom of speech.
To distract the opponent,
you can do trash talk.
Rule number three!
Without completing the challenge, if you
pick up your gun or knife out of anger,
you won't be considered as a man
and will be pronounced as a woman,
and we'll pin flowers to your head.
Your name will be changed to Gomathi.
And you'll have to wear yellow
color Pommy's night dress.
Yours truly, Slap Hand Association.
Both of you, come inside.
First, do you wish
to touch my hand?
Come on, take a look.
Hey, he's mocking you and
you're giving him a chance.
You should never
lose your focus.
Okay, okay. I'll take care.
Don't just blurt out
words. Prove it in action.
Are you a doctor?
He's a doctor
and I'm the police.
You don't need to know.
You have soft hands, idiot.
He broke your hands
in just one blow.
Okay!
If you look at the procedure,
you may get scared.
Bhagat, pick up that towel
and hold it in front of his face.
He couldn't stand a chance.
But came down preaching
me about fighting.
Bloody, broke his
hand with just one blow.
Useless moron!
We'll run a check-up
after two weeks.
Until then, please be careful.
I have another request.
It's better if you
bury the hatchet.
Don't pull in more
people into this mess.
Understood? Don't bring
more people to fight him.
Have a seat, please.
Everybody, meet Mr. Varun.
Our new associate.
We'll be venturing into a
new market with his support.
Now the reason you have been
called here today is to inform
that each one of you have
to deliver five girls in five days.
I know it's not an easy task.
But we have no choice.
As promises have been made.
Thank you all for coming.
Terry…
we need to talk.
Varun, please join us.
Terry, the appointment
has been fixed at 4:00 p.m. today.
Okay.
Thanks.
I have known Melvin for seven years.
Where's Alvin?
He's not well.
Actually, they're twins.
Powerful. Smart.
-And more importantly, loyal.
-Oh!
Tell me. What is it?
I've been facing some issues.
I won't be able to deliver
the five girls you had asked for.
I need some time.
Cookies.
Bastard!
You were not in touch
with Alvin for two weeks.
And there has been no activity
whatsoever from your side.
So, someone is holding Alvin as hostage…
and they have sent you to kill me.
Who is it?
If I reveal their identity,
they'll kill Alvin.
I can't tell you anything.
Tell me, what do I have to do?
Give up all the girls
you have kidnapped.
And drop them off
from where you abducted them.
Don't be scared.
Tell me, who is it?
There's no way you can save us.
They are very close to you.
-Who is that big shot?
-That's the problem.
There is no big shot.
They are ordinary people.
Before you find them…
they would have destroyed you.
Excuse me.
You killed him!
He gave me a clue already.
That's enough.
This the last batch of girls
delivered by Melvin.
I want to know about
the families and friends of these girls.
I want to know where they are
and what they are up to right now.
You have three days' time.
Hey, why are you hovering
the sambar like that?
I got hurt, Gabbar. You chill!
-What happened?
-My hand got jammed in the door.
Does that mean your eyes
were stuck up your butt?
Maybe.
Get lost!
Hey, pour me some sambar.
Why are you walking
as though you're on a ramp?
Take your hands out of your pocket.
-What happened to you?
-I bit my hand while having food.
I bit one hand. So, I used
the other one to eat…
and ended up biting that too.
Shall I feed you?
You can bite my hands too!
Idiot! Get lost!
What are you guys up to?
Everyone has suffered similar injuries.
Are you taking money from me
and working for someone else?
Tell me!
Answer me!
Brother… it's just a game.
Game?
-Slap hand.
-Slap hand?
What is that?
Aren't you ashamed to have
injured yourselves over this game?
If this happens ever again,
I'll fire everyone!
Get lost!
Listen, Gabbar.
I'm leaving this job right away.
Bye, guys!
What are you going to do
after quitting the job?
I'm going to seek revenge, bro.
I'm going to break his hand.
I can't take this anymore.
I will never forget
the things he said about my mom!
Who the hell is it?
He has messed everyone up!
Brother, he's a nobody. Let it go.
Let it go?
Hey, he cussed out my mom!
What did my mom do?
Would you keep quiet
if he cussed at your mom?
I'll break open his head, dude!
Have you gone mad?
Mad?
I don't think you get it properly.
In the end, he mentioned one thing.
He was asking for men to face him.
He said that to me!
Where will I go to find men?
Do I look like a woman to him?
Do you have any men?
Where can I find him?
Sir, it's just a silly game.
And this game doesn't suit you.
I heard that no
one can defeat you.
I want to defeat you.
That's a silly wish.
If you can't, then you
might harm me later.
I'm scared!
I have to play this game.
-I have to break your hand.
-Sir, please don't do it.
Sir, please don't do it.
Sir, please!
Hear me out, don't do it.
You've entered the ring!
Sir, only one leg
is inside the ring.
If you wish to play, hop in
with both the legs, damn it!
Bloody, hulk, step inside.
I'll be respectful
only outside the ring.
Once you step in,
I won't respect you.
Do you have grudge against
him? You got him webbed now.
-Who's going first?
-Come on, Gabbar.
-Yes. Don't spare him.
-You're too bulked up.
-But no play.
-Come on, Gabbar. Concentrate.
-Come on, bring it on!
-Ready?
Keep at it. You're doomed, man!
-Look at his physique.
-Don't give up. That's the way.
Your hand will turn inwards.
Out of the world. Just
finish him, Gabbar.
Your hands and
legs are shivering.
-Awesome!
-Oh, no!
-He's striking like a lightning.
-Come on, Gabbar!
You broke everyone’s'
hand in the city.
Life is a boomerang!
Come on, break his hand!
That's a lot of spit.
Gabbar, he's playing dirty.
He might even end
up peeing on you.
Make sure you're
ready to face anything.
Sir, let not do it.
I'm really scared.
-I don't want to do it.
-What? I don't get it.
Hey, he's just
too great a fighter.
I told you right that
he'll distract you.
-I'm going to rip you apart.
-Faster!
-I'm going to break your hands.
-Come on, brother!
Hey, focus on his hands, damn it
Bloody poker face.
I'm going to thrash you.
Gabbar, quick. Take
you hands away.
Keep at it!
No matter how much you
hit me, I can bear the pain.
You'll bear the pain, is it?
Wait and watch.
Your eyes won't just tear up.
They'll be gouged out of your skull!
He's crying.
-Hey, I'm not crying.
-Oh, really?
Your tears have rolled
down to your pants.
Gabbar, you cried. It's over.
Don't fool around.
-Hey, I'm not crying.
-Gabbar, don't lie.
Why are you being so stubborn?
Useless buffoon!
Don't you understand, damn it?
Gabbar has bit the dust!
Mr. Gabbar, didn't you read the rules?
Flowers are pinned to his head.
Gomathi, why are you glaring at me?
Rightfully, you should
be staring at your men.
But if I mention one thing,
you might get angry.
But it's a fact that these
flowers look pretty on you.
Can I take a selfie with you?
Gomathi, does it hurt?
Gomathi, I'm talking to you.
Does it hurt?
She'll tell you if it really hurts.
Stop tapping on the hand
and begin the procedure.
Gomathi, sister, please
let us know, if it hurts.
Pratap!
Please, open this.
-Put it inside.
-Me?
I won't be good, if
Gomathi looks at it.
Put it inside.
Now, you can
continue to apologize.
I don't see a need for it now.
Maybe I'll get some jasmine,
you can insert them into his nose.
Hey, can't you close the
door, when you're on the toilet.
-I thought of something.
-What is it?
What if all them belong
to the same family.
And one of their own went missing
and they set out to look for her…
and hired us because
they were short of people.
Hey, why would you
think something like that?
Obviously, from the looks of it,
I don't feel we're here to kidnap.
It looks like we're
here to save someone.
There's no logic to
what you're saying.
If so, then whose
daughter is it?
Obviously, it's
Sumathi's daughter.
Hey, Sumathi, doesn't
look like a married woman.
She looks like a student
doing her 2nd year in college.
Right! She's in 2nd year.
And you're in 1st year
and I'm in kindergarten.
Mahali, our lives are at stake.
Killi, my love is at stake.
-Hey, get lost.
-If she comes to know, she'll be hurt.
Sorry, please don't
take it to your heart.
He's a fool.
He was wrong, but
you caught it right.
That's why you are the boss!
Hats off!
Such a meticulous plan…
but he deduced it
sitting on a commode.
Actually, he's the boss!
And it's better for us, if
we lock him inside the toilet.
Terry, that girl's family
is staying at our resort.
You guys are hogging like mad.
No one seem to care,
if he has eaten or not.
Are you worried about him?
Isn't he working
hard for our sake?
When he can do so much,
he surely knows how to eat too.
You better eat.
Park the romance for now.
And focus on finding your niece.
Everyone, sit down.
I'm sure they're not
capable of pulling it off.
There's someone above
them calling the shots.
What if it's him?
I feel he's the root
cause for all our problems.
Well, then, invite him
for the lunch too.
Sit.
If someone slaps a girl,
people tend to look at it.
Instead, if you continue to
eat soup, won't he suspect us?
If you could reach at my
dining table, with fools like him…
you must be a
dangerous criminal.
What if I'm truly a
dangerous gangster?
Unaware, you might kill me.
And then, my men might
come and kill you all.
What would you do then?
Do you think I'll believe you?
You did believe
me all this while.
Mahali…
as he knows everything,
he won't believe me it seems.
I don't get it.
I conned him just
like I conned you.
You couldn't find
out. But he found out.
Did you con us?
-Hey, Killi.
-Last night I warned you.
But now you look shocked!
At least follow now and see
if you can make sense of it.
What about Sumathi?
Sumathi, Gomathi
were part of the plan.
Pass me the pepper. It's your
last supper. Eat it and die.
Not bad, I can see
fear in your eyes.
Don't worry, I won't kill her.
She is business.
But I'll kill each one of you.
Not like you expect it to be.
But like how I wish it to be
How long will it take?
I'm asking because
I'm feeling nauseous.
Do you at least have lemons?
I'm the reason
you people are in this mess.
Let me apologize to everyone.
Please!
Hold on, dear. You don't
have to apologize to me.
Do you know why?
It's because you're
your mother's daughter.
Okay, Uncle.
Do you what that makes you?
That makes you Sumathi's brother.
I even got beaten
up in the process.
I even got bitten twice.
I should be apologizing to you.
I failed in this
mission to save you.
-As a police--
-At least don't lie to the kid.
As a friend of the police, I feel
ashamed to have failed you.
-Uncle.
-Shut up! Don't call me "uncle".
Couldn't you wait for your
folks if the school was over?
You left the school alone,
and someone kidnapped you.
And to save you, he kidnapped me.
And now, someone has kidnapped all of us.
You're such an annoying kid!
To hell with your sorry!
Just get lost!
I haven't been home for six months.
I know you too have the
same opinion about me.
Do you even know why
I left early from school?
In my family, except for me,
no one else would support you.
I knew if I was gone too,
then you'd be left in despair.
Do you know why
I came looking for you?
I know. You did it for Mini's sake.
No, I did it for your sake.
Really?
I like you a lot, Chinnu.
Thanks.
Oh, you're going to burn us alive!
Great, I'll burn and take solace in the
flames, and dance my heart away!
Look, what your
love has done to us.
Hey, why are you being
stingy with the logs?
Get more to burn us.
I think I'll die of heat before
you guys burn me down.
Picked the wrong day
to wear tight undies.
Put some wood out here.
Dude, help me out.
Make sure the knot is tight.
If not, I might fall into the sea.
Hey, stop right there.
I think he wants a re-match.
I'm going to rip him apart.
All these years, I never
asked you for anything.
But now, I have a request.
Brother, can you do
me one last favor?
Even in this dire situation?
Please you move to the other
side and let Varun come to this side.
Brother, can't you grant
me this one last favor?
Sister, they have crucified me.
And you expect
me to move around.
Don't you have any conscience?
Shut up and stay put.
Then ask Varun to come to this
side and you get to the other side.
Do you think he's comfortable
and cozy out there?
Can't you see that
he's been tied up too?
We're about to die and
you're in a romantic mood.
I'm on my death bed.
Please don't irritate me.
Did you say you're at Chetpet?
Help me, Lord!
Fine, look at him.
Your hair is blocking my view.
I don't have time
to cut my hair.
Mad woman, make the
best out of the situation.
Varun!
Varun, unintentionally
I've troubled you a lot.
Please forgive me!
-Chinnu, don't be scared.
-Mom!
Stay strong as always.
My blessings will
always be with you.
Chinnu… when we're on
fire, please close your eyes.
Close your ears too.
When I'm on fire,
I'll scream like hell.
Hey, bring me the petrol.
-Ready!
-Go and get my father.
Headshot! What the shit?
To complete this operation,
you performed that operation.
Oh!
Sir.
Your father is inside that bag.
Think about it.
Alvin, I'm sure you
must be aware…
that he must've
manipulated me to kill Melvin.
Sir, I might say a
million things to survive.
That doesn't mean
you can kill his brother.
Or do you think he'll spare
you for killing his brother?
Alvin, let's discuss
this among ourselves.
-But first, let's kill them all.
-How is that possible?
If he has put your dad inside a
bag and is pointing a gun at him…
this is all part of
my meticulous plan.
So, I believe he must
be a bit loyal to me.
In case, out of anger
if I ask him to shoot…
he might shoot him.
It was you who had mentioned…
that he's very loyal.
Set them free.
Come on! Hurry up!
You guys settle your
score. We're leaving.
Alvin, I know that
you're outraged.
So, I'll make you a better deal.
Spare my father,
and kill me instead.
If I kill you…
then how will you realize
the pain of losing a loved one?
-So, this has to happen.
-What do you mean?
Mom, I think we
left one girl, behind.
Fine, the kids are hungry,
please ask them to hurry up.
It's just one girl.
We managed to save the others.
If you go back to
save that one girl…
you won't come back alive.
Take it that I'm being selfish.
I want to get married to you.
I want to live with you.
Sir.
Sir, can we hold this girl as
hostage to bring him back?
I'm in this situation
because I hired fools like you.
After such a debacle…
do you really think
he'll come back for her?
Fool!
I left one girl behind.
I'm here to take her with me.
How dare you came back for her?
You took away all
the girls from me.
You killed my father too.
And now, you're here to
take away that one last girl too.
I don't get it.
Are you a psycho who
loves to save people?
Who the hell are you?
Police?
Intelligence Bureau?
RAW?
Who are you?
Doctor!
You came here prepared to die.
If I shoot you right now,
you'll die in peace.
So, before you die…
witness the girl getting hacked to pieces.
Nazeer!
You returned to save her, right?
Nazeer, kill her!
Hold!
He must witness the girl
getting hacked before he dies.
Michael, come on! Finish her off.
As long as I live…
you cannot kill that girl.
If you wish to kill her…
you'll have to kill me first.
Kevin.
Shoot me…
and take her!
Terry, I'm very sorry for saying this…
but you're on an ego trip.
It's not safe for us.
Let's kill him first.
And then, we'll kill the girl.
My point exactly.
This was never part of the plan.
I'm also surprised like you.
It is the outcome of my good deeds…
that has saved me today.
Anyway…
goodbye!
Thanks.
Doctors are not the only saviors.
Even the doctors need saviors!
Guys, let's finish this!
THREE MONTHS LATER
CHENNAI
-Hello?
-Bhagat, at least now return our kidneys.
Listen, fool! This is why
education is important.
You must have skipped school as a child,
and now you're making my life difficult!
It's impossible to take
out kidneys just like that!
I don't understand.
He just slit your abdomen
and stitched it up. That's it!
Your kidney is safe and sound.
Get a scan done and check it yourself.
Bloody idiot! Don't call me again.
Son, the police is here.
Didn't you people file
a missing complaint?
Don't you follow-up
after filing a complaint?
I'm talking to you people.
So, we gotta work hard,
nab the accused and present to you, right?
We found the kidnapper.
-How did he find him?
-Hey, bring him here!
Moron!
Oh!
They just caught him now!
I think it'll take them another
five years to find Terry.
Even Chinnu would've got
married by that time.
Ignore him.
The auspicious time is about to end.
You should first get married.
Go on your honeymoon, create
TikTok videos and send them to me.
I'll enjoy watching them.
TikTok has been banned, Bhagat.
What! When did they ban TikTok?
Who gave them the permission
to ban it? I never got an email!
Forget TikTok, we'll shoot
a live duet! Come on.
TikTok has been banned, my dear!
Come to me, my dear!
Let's sing a duet
Enough of being strict, my darling!
Why don't you talk sweetly, my dear?
Hey, sweetheart!
Your body glows like gold
Hold me in a warm embrace
And pinch me slowly
Hey, darling!
Your eyes are like guns
Come and shoot me bit by bit
This is a dangerous age
You have been troubling me
No matter how strong I am
I keep falling for you
My heart is made of glass
You pelted it with stones
Even if it breaks
You'll stay with me forever
You are a doll
You are the embodiment of beauty
You have been made for me
You are a handsome hunk
You are super cool
We truly are made for each other
Generally, I'm as calm as Dhoni
But I can't contain my excitement today
Trap me in your love
Come and enchant me, my dear!
I'm the one for you, darling!
TikTok has been banned, my dear!
Come to me, my dear!
Let's sing a duet
Enough of being strict, my darling!
Why don't you talk sweetly, my dear?
I don't need an umbrella
When you are with me in the rains
You are tempting me and enticing me
I'm completely captivated by you
With your warm smile
You are melting my stony heart
You are mesmerizing me, my love!
Your words are so sweet
I could turn them to poetry
Your eyes shine so bright
They are the light of my life
I will worship you endlessly
This is a dangerous age
You have been troubling me
No matter how strong I am
I keep falling for you
My heart is made of glass
You pelted it with stones
Even if it breaks
You'll stay with me forever
Sweetheart!
You are a doll
You are the embodiment of beauty
You have been made for me
You are a handsome hunk
You are super cool
We truly are made for each other
Generally, I'm as calm as Dhoni
But I can't contain my excitement today
Trap me in your love
Come and enchant me, my dear!
I'm the one for you, darling!
TikTok has been banned, my dear!
Come to me, my dear!
Let's sing a duet
Enough of being strict, my darling!
Why don't you talk sweetly, my dear?
Hey, sweetheart!
Your body glows like gold
Hold me in a warm embrace
And pinch me slowly
Hey, darling!
Your eyes are like guns
Come and shoot me bit by bit